Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Ashwin Kumar. M.R 🔘 Featured

Full Stack .Net Developer with 7 years and 4 Months of experience, B.Tech/B.E in Computers, currently living in Bengaluru / Bangalore.



Current Designation: Full Stack .Net Developer Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Sonata Software Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: net core,.net,asp.net webapi,ASP.Net

MVC, ASP. Net, React. Js, Angular, Javascript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Razor, SQL Server, Mongo DB, AWS

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

I am working as a Full Stack DotNet Developer. I am having proficiency in client side and server side programming. I worked in multiple organizations in various projects. I am result-oriented Professional with over 7 years of experience in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, C#,. Net Core, WebApi, Asp. Net MVC, NodeJs, ReactJs, Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript.

Work Experience

Sonata Software as Full Stack .Net Developer

May 2019 to Till Date

I am working as a Full Stack Dotnet Developer. I am working on serverside and client side technologies both.

Mindtree as Senior Software Engineer

Jun 2013 to Apr 2019

I am working as a Full Stack Dotnet Developer. I am working on serverside and client side technologies both.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Bapuji Institute of Engineering and Technology, Davangere in 2012

IT Skills

#,.Net Core, WebApi
sp.Net MVC, Asp.Net, NodeJs
eactJs , Angular, JavaScript
ypeScript, Razor, Html
ql Server, No Sql - MongoDb
WS S3
OCKER
IS test, XUnit and NUnit
itlab, Github
FS, Tortoise SVN
ISUAL STUDIO
ql server management studio
IICRO SERVICES
zure Logic Apps

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Proficient			
Kannada	Expert			
Telugu	Proficient			

Projects

1/22/2021

Project Title: Trips TUI

Client: TUI

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Role: Other

Duration: May 2019 - Till Date
Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 7

Skill Used: Asp.Net Core, ReactJs, C#, SQL, Rabbit Mq, Entity Framework, GitLab and GitHub, Jira, Code First Approach

Role Description: Full Stack .Net Developer

Project Details: This project is the pricing engine for TUI. There will be two independent versions of Facit NG. One version that is live for Nordics and another which will be part of the TUI Group Solution (TRIPS).

Project Title: AMERICAN REDCROSS

Client: American Redcross Nature of Employment: Full Time Role: Other

Duration: Oct 2018 - Apr 2019 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 20

Skill Used: WebApi, Angular 5, C#, SQL, Entity Framework, GitHub, Jira, Code First Approach.

Role Description: Full Stack .Net Developer

Project Details: American Redcross is a gift management system. Gifts data collected from various vendors are processed and maintained. Donors and their related information were also stored. Admin will be managing all the modules, gift information, user details and access permissions.

Project Title: AXENTIS ENTERPRISE Client: State Street, Merck, Astrazeneca

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Apr 2017 - Sep 2018 Role: Other Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 13

Skill Used: Asp.Net, C#, Javascript, SQL, JQuery, M-ticket, Team Foundation Server, Database first Approach.

Role Description: Full Stack .Net Developer

Project Details: Axentis Enterprise provides on-demand software and solutions for enterprise governance, risk and compliance (GRC) applications. It works on a Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) model, solution for legal and regulatory

compliance and IT Governance and operational activities.

Project Title: NAVEX GLOBAL

Client: Navex Global

Duration: Jan 2016 - Mar 2017 Nature of Employment: Full Time

Role: Other Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 10

Skill Used: Asp.Net MVC, C#, Javascript, SQL,Jira, Github

Role Description: Full Stack .Net Developer

Project Details: It was a case management system. Cases coming from various sources are managed and dispatched. It was

the product of Navex Global.

Project Title: Polaris Client: Polaris

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jun 2014 - Dec 2015

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Role: Other

Team Size: 8

Skill Used: Asp.Net MVC, C#, Javascript, SQL Role Description: Full Stack .Net Developer

Project Details: It was a Web Application, related to Health Care Domain. It was a very huge project with various functionality. If a user wants to make a research, he must pick available doctors and scientists from the pool. The employees are provided

with various permissions, role-based authentication, themes based on locality of employee.

Project Title: Happy Trip

Client: Mindtree

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jun 2013 - May 2014

Role: Other Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 5

Skill Used: Asp.Net, C#, Javascript, SQL Role Description: Full Stack .Net Developer

Project Details: It was Asp.Net Web application, for the purpose of online flight booking. Using this application, user can book flights, search flights, book hotel rooms, search for nearby sightseeing places. It has role-based authentication, locality-based

theme, integration with payment gateway, online ticket receiving, email implementation etc.

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time